fashionproject.com 2015-09-15

# Privacy Policy | Fashion Project

This privacy statement describes how Fashion Project collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

#####  Location Services 

We do not request, collect, or access your location information. 

#####  Collection and Use 

We collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number 
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address 
  * Financial Information such as bank or brokerage account numbers, types of investments 
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password 
  * Preferences Information you provide such as product or content interests, or communication or marketing preferences 
  * Usage activity about how you interact with us such as purchase history, what content you viewed, and which areas of our site you visited. 
  * Device Information 

We also collect the following information from you: 

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type 
  * Demographic information such as household income, age, education, gender, interests, and zip code 
  * Information about your mobile device such as your mobile device id (similar to a website IP address), device type, and mobile service carrier. 

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. 

We use this information to: 

  * Fulfill your order 
  * Send you an order confirmation 
  * Assess your needs to determine suitable products or services 
  * Send you requested product or service information 
  * Send product updates or warranty information 
  * Respond to customer service requests 
  * Administer your account 
  * Send you push notifications when you are using our app. If you do not want these notifications, you can manage your preference either through your device or app settings depending on your device type. You can also contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com). 
  * Send you a newsletter 
  * Send you marketing communications 
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won 
  * Improve our App and marketing efforts 
  * Conduct research and analysis 
  * Respond to your questions and concerns 
  * Display content based upon your interests 

Choice/Opt-Out 

You may opt-out of receiving our newsletter or marketing emails from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each newsletter or marketing email or you can contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com). 

Social Networks 

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others within your network. We cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Also we cannot guarantee that the content you post on our site will not be viewed by others outside your network. 

Information Obtained from Third Parties 

  * We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud. 
  * We purchase marketing data about our customers from third parties and combine it with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products. 
  * We obtain credit information about you from an outside credit reporting agency to help us with customer authentication and credit-related decisions. 
  * If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. 

#####  Sharing Your Information 

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

We may disclose your personal information 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process. 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. 
  * if Fashion Project is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

We make your personal information available to other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to make your personal information available to these companies, contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com). 

#####  Tracking and Ads 

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our App or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Apps to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. 

#####  Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number) to us, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com)

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#####  Other Information 

Our App offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so. 

Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information 

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com). 

Notification of Privacy Statement Changes 

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

#####  Contact 

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below: 

Fashion Project  
88 Black Falcon Ave  
Ste 188  
Boston, MA 02210  
United States  
Email: [info@fashionproject.com](mailto:info@fashionproject.com)  
Phone: (844) 670-1009
